(Sheldon:)We accept your challenge.
Name a time and place.
- Tomorrow, 3:00, the kinetics lab.
- Make it so.
(Leonard:)No, don't make it so.
(Leonard:)Barry, we can't fight you tomorrow.
Our engineer is incapacitated.
(Kripke:)What's wrong with him?
(Raj:)He's depressed because he's pathetic
and creepy and can't get girls.
We're all pathetic and creepy
and can't get girls.
That's why we fight robots.
(Kripke:)If you're not there,
you'll be exposed to ridicule.
(Raj:)I'm curious, what part of America
is that accent from?
- Hey.
- Hey, you got a minute?
(Penny:)Yeah, come on in. What's up?
- I need you to apologize to Howard...
- Get out.
(Leonard:)Come on. Wolowitz won't come out of his
house and we need him for a robot battle.
(Penny:)Then have the robot go and get him.
- The robot didn't hurt his feelings.
- His feelings needed to be hurt.